<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<labels>
<!--FGases QA -->
    <span i18n:translate="">Validation report for F-Gases compliance checks</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Company name/(metric tonnes)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Purchases from Community co-producers</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Sales to Community co-producers</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Producer And Importer Form</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Company Information</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Report status</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Certified</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">In progress</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The report is not yet certified</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Transaction year</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Fluorinated greenhouse gas transaction(s)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">HFC Production</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">PFC Production</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">SF6 Production</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">HFC Import</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">PFC Import</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">SF6 Import</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">NIL report</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">selected</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">not selected</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Missing gases</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The validation is passed successfully.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The delivery is not acceptable. Please see the QA output.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The delivery is acceptable but some of the information has to be checked. Please see the QA output.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The delivery is acceptable.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The delivery status is unknown.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Hide details</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Show details</span>
    <span i18n:translate="feedback-err-src-xml">Could not execute the script because the source XML is not available: <span i18n:name="xml-url"/></span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your delivery did not pass some important checks. In the following sections you will find more information on these errors.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">It is necessary that you correct the blocking errors found by changing your questionnaire before finalizing the delivery!</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The quality check found some issues that may need to be followed-up with your company at a later stage. You don''t have to change your data at present.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">A</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">B</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">C</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">D</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">E</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">F</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">G</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">H</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">I</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">J</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">K</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">L</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">M</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">N</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">O</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">P</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Q</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">R</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">S</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">T</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">U</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">V</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">W</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">X</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Y</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Z</span>

<!-- from rules xquery -->
    <span i18n:translate="">A+B-C+D+E-F+G+H-I-K-L-M</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">A-B+C+D-E-F-G-H</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">A+B-C+D+E-F+G+H-I-K-L</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">A+B-C+D+E-F+G+H-I-K-L</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">O+P+Q+R+S+T+U</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">K+L+M+N+O+P+Q</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">N+O+P</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">N+O+P+Q</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">C+F+N</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">B+J</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">C+F+M</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">C+F+M</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Blocking errors:</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The quality check found important inconsistencies and/or errors in the reported data which need to be fixed.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">No blocking errors have been found.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The check has calculated the sum across all gases of 'Total new production from your facility/ies' as reported in the questionnaire and has found it to be above one tonne. In such a case your company must report as a producer. If the reported data are correct,please tick on the producer box for your respective gas group(s) under the tab 'Company Information', else change your reported data as appropriate.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The check has calculated the sum across all gases of 'Amount imported into the Community' and has found it to be above one tonne. In such a case you must report as an importer. Please tick on the importer box for your respective gas group(s) under the tab 'Company information', else change your reported data as appropriate.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The check has calculated the sum across all gases of 'Amount exported for sale outside the Community' and has found it to be above one tonne. In such a case you must report as an exporter. Please tick on the exporter box under the tab 'company information', else change your reported data, as appropriate.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please check the total amounts exported for recycling, reclamation and /or destruction. It must be smaller than or equal to the exported totals of the respective gas.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The amount reported for export of this gas in the 'Exporter Form' does not match the amount reported for export of this gas in the respective 'Producer/Importer Form'. Please, modify your data where appropriate in order to ensure that both amounts are equal.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The amount reported for export of this gas in this form does not match the amount reported for total export of this gas in the 'Exporter Form'. Please, modify your data where appropriate in order to ensure that both amounts are equal.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You did not tick to be a producer in this gas group under the tab 'Company Information'. Thus you cannot report on production. If you want to report on production, please first revisit the 'Company Information' tab and modify your settings on your production activities there.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You report on "other or unknown" intended applications. Please, provide an explanation in this box.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please complete the name of Co-producer.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You added a new preparation. The sum of the percentages does not equal 100 %. Please correct the figures.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You added a new preparation. The new preparation is identical with another preparation on the list. Please, select the preparation from the drop-down list.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The amounts of the reported gas as stocks on the 1 January in your present report should be consistent with the amounts reported as stocks on the 31 December in your previous year's report. Please change your reported data accordingly or provide an explanation (in the comment field below the reported data under relevant tab of the questionnaire) for the difference in the reported stock amounts.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The amounts of the reported gas as stocks 1 January in your present report should be consistent with the amounts reported as stocks 31 December in your previous year's report. Please note that you should not report on your full stocks but only on that share that was previously imported by your own company. Please change your reported data accordingly or provide an explanation why your reported data is in fact plausible.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your stock increase between 1 January and 31 December for the gas appears to be implausibly high. It should be smaller than or equal to the sum of Production, Import, Collection for reclamation and destruction, Purchases from Co-producers and Other EU purchases. Please change your reported data accordingly or provide an explanation (in the comment field below the reported data in the webform) why your reported data is in fact plausible.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your stock increase between 1 January and 31 December for the gas appears to be implausibly high. It should be smaller than or equal to your Imports. Please note that you as a non-producing company should report only only those stockpiled quantitites which were previously imported by your company. Please change your reported data accordingly or provide an explanation (in the comment field below the reported data in the webform) why your reported data is in fact plausible.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your 'Calculated total' for this gas is lower than the 'Total amount placed on the EU market'. It should be higher or equal to the total amount placed on the market. Please change your reported primary data to make both sums fit accordingly.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your 'Calculated total' for this gas differs from the 'Total amount placed on the EU market'. It should be equal to the total amount placed on the market. Please change your reported primary data accordingly to make both sums fit.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please click the 'Certify correctness' button in the sheet 'finish' before submitting.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The allowed range of years is 2007 until current year.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At least one activity must be selected.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">If NIL report is selected, then no other activities can be selected.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">In the tab 'Company information' you ticked that you are a producer in this gas group but in the tab referring to this gas group you did not report any production quantities. Please report the produced quantities or un-tick the producer box for this gas group.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">In the tab 'Company information' you ticked to be an importer in this gas group but in the tab referring to this gas group you did not report any imported quantities. Please check the imported quantities or un-tick the importer box for this gas group.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You ticked to be an exporter in the sheet 'company information' but no amount of export is considered. Please check the data or untick the export box.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please enter only plain figures into the cells.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please enter only positive figures into the cells.</span>

    <span i18n:translate="">Potential errors:</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The quality check found some issues that may need to be followed-up with your company at a later stage. You don't have to change your data at present.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">No potential errors have been found.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please do not use more than three decimal places for your entry in metric tons.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The amounts of the reported gas as stocks 1 January in your present report is not consistent with the amounts reported as stocks 31 December in your previous year's report. (Explanation provided)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your stock increase between 1 January and 31 December for the gas appears to be implausibly high. It should be smaller than or equal to the sum of Production, Import, Collection for reclamation and destruction, Purchases from Co-producers and Other EU purchases. (Explanation provided)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your stock increase between 1 January and 31 December for the gas appears to be implausibly high. It should be smaller than or equal to your Imports. Please note that you as a non-producing company should report only only those stockpiled quantitites which were previously imported by your company. (Explanation provided)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">In your last year's submission you reported on 31 December stocks of the gases listed above. That's why these gases were expected in your present report as well. In case you are still an importer or producer in the respective gas group(s) (HFCs/PFCs/SF6), please add these gases to your selection and complete the reporting.</span>

<!-- from LABELS xml -->
    <span i18n:translate="">Company contact information</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Reporting HFC production and import data</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Producer and Importer Form 1 &amp; 2: HFCs</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Co-Producer Form 1, 2 (only for producers)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Importer Form 3: HFC preparations*</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Producer and Importer Form: SF6</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Co-Producer Form: SF6</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Producer and Importer Form: PFCs</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Co-Producer Form: PFCs</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Exporter Form (all fluorinated greenhouse gas types)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Transactions/(metric tonnes)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total new production from your facility/ies</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount imported into the Community</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount exported for sale outside the Community</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Other amounts collected for reclamation or destruction from within the Community</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Purchases from Community co-producers</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Sales to Community co-producers</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount purchased from other Community sources</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Stocks held at 1 January</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Stocks held at 31 December</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount reclaimed by your company</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount destroyed by your company (on-site)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount destroyed on your behalf (off-site within the Community)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Amount used as a feedstock by your company</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Calculated total</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Refrigeration and air-conditioning</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Fire protection</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Aerosols</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Solvents</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Foams</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Feedstock</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Other or unknown</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total amount placed on the Community market</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total sold</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Electrical equipment</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Magnesium die casting operations</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Semiconductor manufacture</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Section 1. Export totals (metric tonnes)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Section 2. Total amount exported for recycling, reclamation and/or destruction (metric tonnes)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Fluorinated greenhouse gas type</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Annual total exported from the European Community</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Recycling</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Reclamation</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Destruction</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">HFC</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">SF6</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">HFCs</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">HFC preparations*</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">PFCs/PFC preparations</span>

<!--FGases/ODS envelope QA -->
    <span i18n:translate="">Check contents of delivery</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your delivery cannot be accepted as you did not complete the online questionnaire as instructed in the BDR user manual.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please create a new envelope, fill in the online questionnaire and re-submit.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The submission cannot be accepted as an envelope can contain either a F-gases questionnaire, not both.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The submission cannot be accepted as an envelope can contain either a ODS questionnaire, not both.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please delete the file(s) you don't want to keep and then retry to submit to DG CLIMA/EEA.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your delivery cannot be accepted as you have provided more than one xml files (you have completed more than one online questionnaires).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please create a new envelope and re-submit using only the correct xml file. Note that if you wish to report for more than one reporting year you have to use separate envelopes.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">For your convenience, you can use the "Copy previous delivery" button in the new envelope to copy existing xml-files from the current (submitted but rejected) envelope.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You have made a submission using the online questionnaire correctly. Your data report (xml-file stored in this envelope) is accepted.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="feedback-additional-files-evaluation-note">Please note that the quality of any additional files included in your delivery will not be evaluated automatically. In case you wish to have an additional evaluation of this data please contact the <span i18n:name="feedback-obligation-short-name">ODS OR F-Gases</span> Reporting support team (<span i18n:name="helpdesk-email-address"/>), providing the link to the current submission (copy and paste the url address of the present webpage).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Your data report has been completed correctly using the online questionnaire.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You have added NIL reporting questionnaire but the report is not certified or the data is invalid on the report. Please revise your report and fix the errors.</span>


<!--ODS QA -->
    <span i18n:translate="">Validation report for Ozone-Depleting Substances compliance checks</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">-empty-</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">-missing-</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Producer</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Importer</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Exporter</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">ProcessAgent</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Feedstock</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Destruction</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Report status</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Report activities</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Transaction year</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">1. Reporting undertaking</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">2. Definition of substances</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">3. Total production</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">4. Production under industrial rationalisation</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">5. Recycling and reclamation by producers</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">6. Quantities received from undertakings in the EU (e.g. purchases)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">7. Total imports from countries or territories outside EU.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">8. Total stocks</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">9. Stocks for selected uses held by producers</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">10. Placing on the EU market during the reporting year (sales etc.)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">11. Exports to countries and territories outside EU</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">12. Feedstock and process agent use within the reporting undertaking</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">13. Use within the reporting undertaking other than process agent or feedstock uses</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">14. Quantities destroyed in your facility</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">15. Accounting Framework</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total quantity available: Table3 (total) + Table6 (total) + Table7 (total) + Table8 (at 1 Jan total)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total Sales / Use / Destruction: Table10 + Table11 + Table12 + Table13 + Table14 + Table8 (at 31 Dec total)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Check sum (Total Available - Total Sales/Use/Destruction)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Comments</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Use</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Transferring undertaking</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Recycling and reclamation (for any uses inside or outside EU)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Supplier</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Customs procedure</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total stocks at the beginning / end of reporting year</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Source country</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Stocks reported in table 8 resulting from production in the reporting year:</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Recipient</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Destination Country</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Processes</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Destruction technology</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Substance</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Code</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Company activities: </span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Current Facility activities: </span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 01 January total</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 31 December total</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 01 January free release</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 31 December free release</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 01 January customs bondage</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 31 December customs bondage</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 01 January destruction</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">At 31 December destruction</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total make-up</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Total emission</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Make-up</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Emission</span>
<!-- ODS QA rules -->
    <span i18n:translate="">Please make sure that you press the 'certify correctness' button in the finish page of the webform, before submitting the report.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Wrong status</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please make sure to select at least one activity. If you have nothing to report, please select NIL report.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">A NIL report cannot be combined with any of the other activities.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Mandatory values must be entered.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Missing value</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Values should be higher than or equal to zero. Decimal signs are not allowed and quantities should always be rounded-up.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Invalid value</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The codes must exist in the corresponding code list.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Please make sure that when you select 'other' as use, this is specified in the text box.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Missing description</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Suppliers and/or recipients of substances have been fully identified (undertaking name, address and country).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Only process agent users can report PAU processes and Feedstock users can report FDST processes.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Invalid process</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Table 5 (recycling and reclamation) should only be filled in if you are an ODS producer. Quantities received from companies for recycling and reclamation need to be reported in Table 6 (quantities received from EU Companies).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">No Total production</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Quantities reported in Table 9 (Stocks for selected uses) have to be equal or less than the stock at the end of the year in table 8. Please note that in Table 9 only stocks resulting from production in the reporting year should be included</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Suspicious Quantity</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Emissions resulting from feedstock or process agent use are higher than zero and are more than 0,1% of the make-up.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Suspicious Emission</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The quantities do not correspond with the license database (value indicated in brackets).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Check licence</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can only be filled in by producers.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Invalid data</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can only be filled in by importers.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can only be filled in by exporters.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can only be filled in by process agent users (only PAU processes) and feedstock users (only FDST processes).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can be filled in by producers, importers, exporters, feedstock users and process agent users</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can be filled only by producers, importers or exporters.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">This table can only be filled in by undertakings destroying substances in their own facility. </span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Table cannot be filled if 'Not obliged to report' is selected.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The quantities do not correspond with the license database (value indicated in brackets).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Check quantity</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Stock at the beginning of the year has to match with the stock at the end of previous year indicated in brackets.</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Stock mismatch</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The accounting framework should be zero. Quantities received, imported, produced and in stock at 1 January of the reporting year should equal quantities placed on the market, exported, used, destroyed and in stock at the end of the year. If the reported quantities are correct but the accounting framework is not zero please provide an explanation in the comment box (on table 'finish').</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Not zero</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">The accounting framework should be zero. Quantities received, imported, produced and in stock at 1 January of the reporting year should equal quantities placed on the market, exported, used, destroyed and in stock at the end of the year. (Explanation provided).</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">You need to provide an EORI code if you are going to report activities related to imports/exports!</span>

    <!-- ODS destructions -->
    <span i18n:translate="">Cement kilns (all controlled substances except BCM, Halons, HBFC, HCFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Liquid injection incineration (all controlled substances except BCM, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Gaseous/fume oxidation (all contolled substances except BCM, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Reactor cracking (all controlled substances except Halons, BCM, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Rotary kiln incineration (all controlled substances except BCM, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Argon plasma arc (all controlled substances except BCM, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Inductively coupled radio frequency plasma (all controlled substances except BCM, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Microwave plasma (all controlled substances except BCM, Halons, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Nitrogen plasma arc (all controlled substances except BCM, Halons, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Gas phase catalytic dehalogenation (all controlled substances except BCM, Halons, HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Superheated stream reactor (all controlled substances except BCM, Halons HBFC, MB)</span>
    <span i18n:translate="">Other destruction technology (only BCM, HBFC, MB) (specify in comments field)</span>
</labels>
